Papers of Morris K. Udall, 1920-1995
University of Arizona Library Special Collections
- Administrative Files, 1961-1990
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1961-1990
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 1-2)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 3-4)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration-Scandal. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration-Green Valley. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration-Minimum Property Standard. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration-"Star Series." 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Office of Interstate Land Sales. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Metropolitan Development Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Federal Disaster Assistance Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Renewal and Hosing Assistance-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 12-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Renewal and Hosing Assistance-Tucson Urban Renewal. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Model Cities. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Housing and Urban Development, Office of Interstate Land Sales. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 18-19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 20-24)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs-Papago Drought. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Office of Petroleum Allocation. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 26)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Oil and Gas. 1973-1974 (Box 573, Folder 27-28)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Land Management-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 1-4)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Land Management-Tucson Mining Claims. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 5-7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Land Management-Planet Town Site. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Land Management-Lower Colorado Office. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Mining Enforcement and Safety Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Outdoor Recreation. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Reclamation-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 12-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Reclamation-Central Arizona Project. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 15-17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Reclamation-Rainbow Bridge. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Bureau of Reclamation-Power Plants. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Fish and Wildlife Service-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Fish and Wildlife Service-Predator Control. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, National Park Service. 1973-1974 (Box 574, Folder 22-24)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Office of Saline Water. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Office of Territories. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Interior, Geological Survey. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Kent State Killings. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Drug Enforcement Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 7-8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Bureau of Prisons. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, FBI. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Board of Parole. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Justice, Immigration and Naturalization Service. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 12-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Labor, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Labor, Manpower Administration-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 16-19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Labor, Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Labor, OSHA-Wage and Labor Standards. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Post Office, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Post Office, Cases. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 23)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Post Office, Commemorative Stamps. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 24)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Post Office, Klassen and Responses to Press Club Speech. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Post Office, Pornography. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 26)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Post Office, Revoking Bulk Mail Permits. 1973-1974 (Box 575, Folder 27)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: State, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 1-4)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: State, Agency for International Development. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Coast Guard. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Federal Aviation Agency. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Federal Aviation Agency-Tucson International Airport. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Urban Mass Transportation Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Federal Highway Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 11-12)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Federal Highway Administration-Traffic Safety. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 13)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, National Transportation Safety Board. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Transportation, Bureau of Public Roads-Urban Mass Transportation. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Treasury, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Treasury, Office of Revenue Sharing. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Treasury, Bureau of Customs. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Treasury, Customs vs. Border Patrol. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Treasury, Internal Revenue Service. 1973-1974 (Box 576, Folder 20-22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, American Revolution Bicentennial Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Atomic Energy Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Civil Aeronautics. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Civil Service Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 4-6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Civil Rights Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Consumer Product Safety Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Corporation for Public Broadcasting. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Economic Stabilization, Pay Board. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Economic Stabilization, Price Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies,Economic Stabilization-Cost of Living Council. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 12-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Environmental Protection Agency-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 15-17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Environmental Protection Agency-Air Quality-Arizona Plan. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 18-19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Environmental Protection Agency-Air Programs Office. 1973-1974 (Box 577, Folder 20-23)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Environmental Protection Agency-Water Programs Office. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Equal Employment Opportunities Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Export-Import Bank. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Communications Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 4-5)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Energy Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 7-8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Energy Office. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 9-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Energy Office-Chaparral, Tucson Gas and Electric. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Home Loan Bank Board. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Power Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Federal Trade Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, General Accounting Office. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, General Accounting Office-Arizona Jobs Consortium. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Government Printing Office. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, General Services Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 23-24)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, General Services Administration-Nogales Border Station. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, General Services Administration-Tucson Federal Building. 1973-1974 (Box 578, Folder 26)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Indian Claims Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Interstate Commerce Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Library of Congress. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Library of Congress-Congressional Research Service. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 4-5)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Aeronautics and Space Administration. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Academy of Sciences. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Credit Union Bureau. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Foundation on Arts and Humanities. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Science Foundation-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 10-11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Science Foundation-Kitt Peak National Observatory. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 12)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Railroad Passenger Corporation. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 13)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, National Water Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Office of Technology Assessment. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 15-17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Overseas Private Investment Corporation. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Postal Rate Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Railroad Retirement Board. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Security and Exchange Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Smithsonian Institution. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Smithsonian Institution-Astrophysical Observatory. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 23)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Small Business Administration-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 24)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Gila River-Pima Reservation. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, United States Information Agency. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 26)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Veterans Administration-Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 27-28)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: Independent Agencies, Water Resources Council. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 29)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: International Agencies, General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 30)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: International Agencies, International Boundary and Water Commission. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 31)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 93rd Congress: International Agencies, United Nations. 1973-1974 (Box 579, Folder 32)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 580, Folder 1-12)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Department of Economic Security. 1975-1976 (Box 580, Folder 13-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Governor's Office. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Land. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 2-5)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Land-ATOM. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Land-Montezuma Estates. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Land-Rancho Romero. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Legislative Digests. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 9-10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, Politics. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, University of Arizona-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 12)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Arizona Agencies, University of Arizona-Solar Energy. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 13)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Executive Agencies, Action. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 14-15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Executive Agencies, Central Intelligence Agency. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 16-17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Executive Agencies, National Security Agency. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Executive Agencies, Office of Economic Opportunity-Yaquis. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Executive Agencies, Office of Management and Budget. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Executive Agencies, White House. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Judiciary, Supreme Court. 1975-1976 (Box 581, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 1-2)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Cotton. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Farmers' Home Administration. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 4-7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Food and Nutrition Service. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 8-9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 10-14)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Hart Prairie. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Proposed Regulations. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-San Francisco Peaks. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-James Watt Timber Sales. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Research Service. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Rural Electrification Administration. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Soil Conservation Service. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Agriculture, Forest Service-Stabilization and Conservation Service. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 23-24)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce-Census Bureau. 1975-1976 (Box 582, Folder 25)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce, Economic Development Administration. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 1-4)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce, Economic Development Administration-Bisbee. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 5-6)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce, Economic Development Administration-Indian Development District of Arizona (IDDA). 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 7-8)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce, National Bureau of Statistics. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Commerce, Patent Office-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 12-15)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Air Force-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 16)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Air Force-Davis-Monthan. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 17-18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Air Force-Hughes Aircraft. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 19-20)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Air Force-UFO. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Army-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 22-23)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Army Corps of Engineers. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 24-25)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Army-Fort Huachuca. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 26-27)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Army-Timberlake, EW. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 28)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Marines-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 29)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, National Guard. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 30-31)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Defense, Navy-Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 583, Folder 32-33)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Health, Education, and Welfare, Miscellaneous. 1975-1976 (Box 584, Folder 1-4)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Health, Education, and Welfare, Aging. 1975-1976 (Box 584, Folder 5-7)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 94th Congress: Health, Education, and Welfare, Busing. 1975-1976 (Box 584, Folder 8-9)